Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Lights Caramel action. Let me
show you how to make it. We're just
going with a classic vanilla protein
shake base. Protein shake, vanilla bean
paste, sweetener, salt, zippering gum.
Then you can just blend that up, throw
it in the freezer, wait about 16 hours,
then take it out, run it under hot
water, and then throw it in your creamy
on the light ice cream setting. While
that's going, we can grab some of our
mixins. These are the Fuel cookie dough
bites. For this recipe, we're using
about a third of a package. Now, back to
the ice cream. We're going to take that
out. It's going to be crumbly most
likely. You can just scrape down the
sides, and then throw it back in the
creamy on the respin setting. Should
come out looking beautiful. So, now all
you have to do is smooth out the top,
top it with that cookie dough and about
half a sheet of graham cracker, and then
drizzle it with your caramel syrup. And
boom. 309 calories, 36 grams of protein,
and so delicious.